Mina Adel Nathan

Midlevel Full-Stack Web Developer

CONTACT MEAT

- mina.adel158@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/mina-adel-676836192
- 01012391979

Wuzzuf code: 1706

minaadel.me

- Mina-Timo-Official
- Ain Shams, Cairo, Egypt

SKILLS SUMMARY

- PHP
- **JavaScript**
- Laravel
- React.is
- Node.js
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- **React Native**
- MySql/MSSql •
- Apache/Nginx
- NoSal
- **AWS**
- Python
- Git/Github
- HTML/HTML5 •
- Docker
- CSS/CSS3

PERSONAL SKILLS

- **Explaining Good interpersonal** and communication skills
- **Team Working**
- Self-Learner
- Self-Motivated
- **Good Research Abilities**

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree

Faculty of Computer and Information Science

Ain Shams University | 2015 - 2019 G P A: 2.5 (GOOD)

Graduation Project:

Passenger-Guide (Grade Excellent)

LANGUAGES

Arabic

English

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full-Stack Developer with a strong ability to collaborate with multiple teams to accomplish various projects. Successfully developed custom solutions to solve challenges and engineered designs to meet predetermined functionality goals. Experience with PHP, Laravel, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Vue.js, MySQL, MSSQL and business continuity solutions. Exceptional written and verbal communication skills as well as personal accountability.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OctopusPro (full stack Developer) | 10/2020 - present Working on:

- Twillio integration for calls, sms and voice mail.
- Xero integration for online accounting software for taxes.
- · Google Maps.
- Aws(S3, RDS, SES, Lambda).
- Payment getways(stripe , Tap)

Tech used(PHP, Zend, mysql, Docker)

Full stack developer

Bidiks.com

Built this website from scratch with two types of authentication (contractor and supplier) and sending emails and notifications and Localization and Chat by pusher. Tech used(PHP, Laravel, mysql).

SaintMaryAndSangeorgeAlSherouk.com

Built from scratch to book mass every number of days where this number is saved on the site config with sending email. Tech used(PHP, Laravel, mysql).

Mufaddal food industry (ERP Developer) | 11/2019 – 10/2020

- Microsoft AXdynamics 2012: create reports for sales and inventories and accountants, and custom modules like HR, sales and inventory, and custom security and roles.
 - Tech used(X++, AOT).
- built from scratch it's a "حبة عبة" : built from scratch sales mobile app for salesmen as it creates invoices and shows there's targets and daily, weekly, monthly and yearly reporting, and generates procedures for collecting the data for reports in mobile app.

Tech used(React Native, MSsql).

Web Services: create APIs to mobile app. Tech used(.Net).

Attendance system: integrated with the fingerprint to save the employee attendance and generates attendance reports.

Tech used(.Net, MSsql).